

### **PROFILE**

As a Loan Administration Officer at Wing Bank branch Pailin city .

My experience includes controlling collaterals, Actually I disburse loan for customer as well and I'm checker. For sure I'm good in Flex-cube system. I am preparing loan document soft copy and hard copy in vault. In addition, I am responsible for controlling report as loan admin.

Finally I'm welling at team work, reliable and hard working. I am flexible and learning something new.

#### CONTACT

#### PHONE:

098308438 / 078987817

#### ADDRESS:

Anlong Pouk Village , Tasanh Commune , Samlout District , Battambang Province , Cambodia

#### EMAIL:

dalinmeas7758@gmail.com dalin.meas@winabank.com.kh

# **HOBBIES**

Travelling, Photo Shooting, Reading book, Listening music and outgoing

# DALIN MEAS

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Dewey International University**

2021 - Aug 2024

Finished Bachelor degree in Finance and Banking.

# Coerr Language Skill Center

January 2023-June 2024

Studied English at level 6

# Samlout High School

2017-2020

Finished diploma and studied English at BFL Foreign Language School

## Samlout Secondary School

2014-2017

Finished secondary class

# Tasanh Primary School

2008-2014

Finished primary class

# QUALIFICATION AND TRAINING COURSE

## June-2024

Received a certificate as outstanding student for Year 3

## December 2023

Completed course in "Business Information System"

Completed some courses at Wing University

- Wing Griding Principal
- Whistleblowing Protection Procedure
- Essential Cyber Security
- Disciplinary & Grievance Procedure
- Foreign Account Tax Compliance Act (FATCA)
- Code of Conduct Ethic
- Operational risk Management
- AML & CFT

Completed course "Responsible for Lending" by Institude of Banking & Finance

#### May 2022

Received a certificate as outstanding student for Academic Year

## 2019-2020

Volunteer of Youth Council at Samlout High School.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### February 2023- Present

Working as Loan administration Officer at Wing Bank for 1 year and 7 months.

- Disbursement loan
- Controlling collaterals
- Checking document before disbursement
- Controlling soft and hard document
- Holding password with vault
- Can use well in Flex-cube system
- Generate PIN for customer
- Opening account for customer ( with loan )
- Controlling report: Master collateral report, CBC report, Post Condition report Loan rejected report, Insurance report

## August 2022 – January 2023

Intern teller at LOLC (Cambodia) Plc in Battambang branch.

- Can use T-24 System
- Check CBC for customer
- Provide service for customer such as pay repayment loan , deposit money , transfer money , explain some issue for customer ,
- Prepare document

#### 2021-2022

Cashier at Green Garden Mart.

- Be a cashier for customer payment money
- Prepare inventory in stock
- Provide good service for customer
- Cleaning items and inventory

## **SKILLS**

- Can use Microsoft word, Excel and Power point
- Good in English language and Khmer language
- Can use and understand about word that use in bank
- Can write , speak , listen English as well
- Good in basic accounting, banking, finance.

# **REFERENCES**

**Khly Leng** Position: District Lending Manager at Wing Bank Pailin

Tell : 078 988 862 / 093 240 003